Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
You would have heard a number of times that string is immutable.
你可能已经听过很多次，字符串是不可变的。
That means the value of string cannot be changed.
这意味着字符串的值不能被改变。
Is that really true?
这真的是真的吗？
Yep, it is true.
是的，它是真的。
So, in this video, let's explore that a little bit further and look at other ways of getting a modified
所以，在这个视频中，让我们进一步探讨这个问题，并看看从一个特定的字符串中获得一个修改过的
string from a specific string.
字符串的其他方法。
Okay. Now, let's type in a simple piece of code String str =  "in28Minutes" and let's say
好的。现在，让我们输入一段简单的代码 String str = "in28Minutes" ，假设
I'm concatenating str.concat("is awesome").
我把str.concat("is awesome")连接起来。
Okay, some self-praise there. But I guess you can ignore that.
好吧，那里有些自我表扬。但我想你可以忽略这一点。
So, what we are doing is str, str.concat("is awesome").
所以，我们正在做的是str，str.concat("is awesome")。
Concat is a function to concat a string content of that specific string with another string.
Concat是一个函数，用于将一个特定字符串的内容与另一个字符串连接起来。
So, here it's
所以，这里是
we said "in28Minutes is awesome". Because there is no space either at the end or here.
我们说 "in28Minutes is awesome"。因为在结尾和这里都没有空格。
It's becoming like a single word.
它变得像一个单字。
I would try and print the content of str.
我将尝试打印str的内容。
What do you think the content of str would be?
你认为str的内容会是什么？
Aha!
啊哈!
It's "in28minutes".
它是 "in28minutes"。
So, the thing is, the content of str has not really changed.
所以，问题是，str的内容并没有真正改变。
So, even though I am calling str.concat("is awesome),
所以，即使我调用str.concat("is awesome)。
the str remains the same.
但str的内容仍然是一样的。
What it does is, it returns another string. So, String anotherString = str.concat, this
它所做的是，它返回另一个字符串。所以，String anotherString = str.concat，这个
time,
次。
let's be very careful.
让我们非常小心。
I'll give a space and say " is awesome". Now, what would happen?
我会给一个空格，然后说" 是真棒"。现在，会发生什么？
You can see that anotherString is assigned this value
你可以看到，anotherString被分配了这个值
and if I print str, it's "in28minutes".
并且如果我打印str，它是 "in28minutes"。
So, whenever I'm trying to modify a value of a string, what we're doing is not really modifying that
所以，每当我试图修改一个字符串的值时，我们所做的并不是真的修改那个
specific string.
特定的字符串。
So, if I'm doing str.concat for a specific string, what we are doing is, we'll create a new
所以，如果我为一个特定的字符串做str.concat，我们正在做的是，我们将创建一个新的
string and return it back. The original string remains unaffected. So, str remains "in28minutes".
字符串并将其返回。原来的字符串不受影响。所以，str仍然是 "in28minutes"。
We are creating anotherString, with the value of the new concatenation.
我们正在创建另一个字符串，用新的连接值。
So, let's say now, I'd say String, instead of calling another string, I'll say string2 = anotherString.
所以，我们现在说，我说String，而不是调用另一个字符串，我会说string2 = anotherString。
I feel that there is, let's say, I would want to append  a "."(dot).
我觉得有，比方说，我想附加一个"."（点）。
I'm saying string2 = anotherString.concat.
我说string2 = anotherString.concat。
What happens is a new string is created, string2 with
发生的情况是一个新的字符串被创建，string2带有
"in28Minutes is awesome" with a dot.
"in28Minutes is awesome "加上一个点。
But if you type in str, it remains "in28Minutes".
但是如果你输入str，它仍然是 "in28Minutes"。
If you type in anotherString, it remains this
如果你输入另一个字符串，它仍然是这样的
and if I type in string2, the value is with a dot. This behavior of a String class is called immutability.
而如果我输入string2，其值是带点的。字符串类的这种行为被称为不变性。
Once an instance of a String class is created with a specific value,
一旦一个字符串类的实例以特定的值被创建，你将永远无法改变。
you will never be able to change the value of that specific variable.
你将永远无法改变这个特定变量的值。
This "in28Minutes" will always remain "in28Minutes".
这个 "in28Minutes "将永远是 "in28Minutes"。
If you try and execute a method on it, it would create a new string. But the original value remains as
如果你试图对它执行一个方法，它将创建一个新的字符串。但是原来的值仍然是
it is. It remains "in28Minutes".
它是这样的。它仍然是 "in28Minutes"。
Okay.
好的。
Now that we discussed this in great detail, let's focus on the other methods that are present in String
现在我们已经非常详细地讨论了这个问题，让我们把重点放在String类中的其他方法上
class to get modified values from the String class.
类中的其他方法来获取String类中的修改值。
Let's start with a simple strings, "in28Minutes is awesome.".
让我们从一个简单的字符串开始，"in28Minutes is awesome." 。
Let's assign that.
让我们把它赋值。
So, now we have a new string, "in28Minutes is awesome."
所以，现在我们有一个新的字符串，"in28Minutes is awesome."
and let's say I would want to make it all uppercase.
假设我想把它变成全大写字母。
How do I do that?
我如何做到这一点呢？
You can have a function called toUpperCase, "in 28Minutes is awesome." and similar to that
你可以有一个叫做toUpperCase的函数，"in28Minutes is awesome. "和类似的函数
guess, what is the function to do a lowercase?
猜猜看，做小写的函数是什么？
Yeah, you're right.
是的，你说对了。
It's lowercase.
它是小写的。
Let's say there is some space at the end of a string and the start of a string.
比方说，在一个字符串的末尾和一个字符串的开头有一些空格。
Let's say there's a string called str2,
比方说，有一个叫str2的字符串。
there is some space at the start and some space at the end
开头有一些空格，结尾有一些空格
and I would want to remove that.
我想把它删除。
How do I do that? str2.trim( ).
我怎么做呢？str2.trim( )。
It removes spaces at the start of a string and at the end of the string. In this video, what we looked
它可以删除字符串开头和结尾的空格。在这个视频中，我们所看到的
at is the fact that, String class is immutable. Any instance of a String class, once it's created in memory,
是这样一个事实，即String类是不可改变的。任何一个字符串类的实例，一旦在内存中被创建，其内容就不能被改变。
the content of that cannot be changed.
它的内容就不能被改变。
We looked at all the different operations which are present in String like toUppercase, toLowercase,
我们研究了所有存在于字符串中的不同操作，如toUppercase、toLowercase。
trim, and concatenate which would help us to get a new string with a modified value of an existing string.
trim和concatenate，它们可以帮助我们用现有字符串的修改值得到一个新的字符串。
I'll see you in the next video where we would be talking about a few more utility methods in the String class.
我们将在下一个视频中看到你，在那里我们将讨论字符串类中的其他一些实用方法。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，拜拜了。